let savollar8 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "anniversary",
      answer: "B. yubiley",
      options: [
        "A. tug'ilgan kun",
        "B. yubiley",
        "C. bayram",
        "D. tantana"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "arithmetic",
      answer: "C. arifmetika",
      options: [
        "A. geometriya",
        "B. algebra",
        "C. arifmetika",
        "D. fizika"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "ashamed",
      answer: "A. uyalgan",
      options: [
        "A. uyalgan",
        "B. mamnun",
        "C. xursand",
        "D. g'urur"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to burst",
      answer: "D. portlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. sinmoq",
        "B. yiqilmoq",
        "C. uzilmoq",
        "D. portlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "carpenter",
      answer: "B. duradgor",
      options: [
        "A. g'isht teruvchi",
        "B. duradgor",
        "C. bo'yoqchi",
        "D. santexnik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "coal",
      answer: "C. ko'mir",
      options: [
        "A. yog'och",
        "B. tosh",
        "C. ko'mir",
        "D. qum"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "couch",
      answer: "A. divan",
      options: [
        "A. divan",
        "B. kursi",
        "C. kreslo",
        "D. stul"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to drip",
      answer: "B. tomchilamoq",
      options: [
        "A. oqmoq",
        "B. tomchilamoq",
        "C. quymoq",
        "D. sachramoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "elegant",
      answer: "D. maftunkor",
      options: [
        "A. oddiy",
        "B. sodda",
        "C. odatiy",
        "D. maftunkor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "fabric",
      answer: "C. mato",
      options: [
        "A. teri",
        "B. plastik",
        "C. mato",
        "D. metall"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "highlands",
      answer: "A. tog'li hudud",
      options: [
        "A. tog'li hudud",
        "B. pastlik",
        "C. vodiy",
        "D. tekislik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "ivory",
      answer: "B. fil suyagi",
      options: [
        "A. suyak",
        "B. fil suyagi",
        "C. shox",
        "D. marmar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "mill",
      answer: "D. tegirmon",
      options: [
        "A. fabrika",
        "B. ustaxona",
        "C. omborxona",
        "D. tegirmon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "needle",
      answer: "C. igna",
      options: [
        "A. qaychi",
        "B. ip",
        "C. igna",
        "D. tugma"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to polish",
      answer: "A. pardozlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. pardozlamoq",
        "B. tozalamoq",
        "C. yuvmoq",
        "D. artmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to sew",
      answer: "B. tikmoq",
      options: [
        "A. to'qimoq",
        "B. tikmoq",
        "C. ilmoq",
        "D. toximoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "shed",
      answer: "D. omborxona",
      options: [
        "A. garaj",
        "B. molxona",
        "C. yerto'la",
        "D. omborxona"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "thread",
      answer: "C. ip",
      options: [
        "A. arqon",
        "B. shnur",
        "C. ip",
        "D. jun"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to trim",
      answer: "A. qisqartirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qisqartirmoq",
        "B. kesmoq",
        "C. qirqmoq",
        "D. olmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "upwards",
      answer: "B. yuqoriga",
      options: [
        "A. pastga",
        "B. yuqoriga",
        "C. yonga",
        "D. oldinga"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export default savollar8;